[00:00.53]A perfect plan?
[00:03.10]When shopping in the United States or Canada,
[00:07.10]people can return an item they have bought for a refund
[00:11.72]if they are not pleased with it.
[00:14.86]Some people will jump at the chance to take advantage of this rule to first meet their needs
[00:23.92]and then later returning the item to get their money back.
[00:29.14]But things don’t always go as planned.
[00:33.81]One day, Judy and her two friends went shopping for the upcoming prom.
[00:41.44]In the Ladies Department, Judy saw a beautiful dress which cost one hundred Canadian dollars.
[00:50.84]She didn’t have enough money at the time and wondered how she could buy it.
[00:58.08]Suddenly, an idea came to her.
[01:03.27]Judy’s father had given her one hundred dollars to buy a new calculator for math class.
[01:11.48]She could use the money to buy the dress, wear the dress to the prom,
[01:18.75]return it for a refund the next day and then get the calculator.
[01:24.97]“What a perfect plan!” she said to herself.
[01:30.21]Judy bought the dress as planned and tried it on at home.
[01:36.47]“It fits well,” she said.「它很(適合)合身。」
[01:39.66]However, as she was putting her make-up on, a piece of lipstick broke off and fell on her dress, leaving a big stain.
[01:52.01]Judy tried to wash the dress, but the stain wouldn’t come off.
[01:59.29]The worst part was that the dress shrank after she washed it.
[02:05.52]The store would never take it back now.
[02:09.74]Judy couldn’t believe that she had messed everything up.
[02:15.97]She didn’t know what she could do now.
[02:20.17]Judy started to worry about how angry her father would be once he found out what had happened.
[02:30.49]She decided to tell her father the truth, and was grounded for two weeks.
[02:37.78]But, Judy learned a good lesson from this experience.
[02:43.01]She learned that one should not have too many wishes beyond one’s means.
[02:50.27]She also learned that one should never lie.
