[00:01.74]People at Work
[00:04.65]Most people have jobs, and they go to work almost every day.
[00:10.98]Some people are very lucky because they can have a lot of fun
[00:17.66]or make a lot of money doing their jobs.
[00:22.25]However, most people are not so lucky
[00:27.49]because their jobs aren’t much fun and don’t make them much money.
[00:33.92]It is often the case that many interesting jobs are very hard.。
[00:41.82]For these kinds of jobs people have to learn how to do the job for a long time
[00:49.91]before they start working.
[00:53.61]For example, doctors study for six or more years after they are finished university.
[01:02.49]Pilots have to study even longer.
[01:06.80]They have to learn to fly small airplanes at the beginning,
[01:12.20]and then slowly they move up to fly bigger and bigger planes.
[01:18.32]Most pilots are over thirty years old
[01:22.38]Some young people have good luck and get to work in interesting and well-paying jobs.
[01:31.98]For example, there are many good athletes who are young.
[01:37.74]Football and tennis players are often under thirty-five years old.
[01:45.40]Older people usually cannot play these sports very well because they cannot move very quickly.
[01:54.98]However, golf is a good sport for older people.
[02:01.41]There are many good golfers who are quite old.
[02:06.34]Many people keep working until they retire at sixty or sixty-five years old.
[02:14.78]When they stop working, they have a lot of free time.
[02:19.72]However, some people never stop working at all.
[02:25.56]These people usually have very interesting jobs
[02:30.49]They have so much fun doing their jobs that they don’t want to give them up.
[02:37.58]For example, many writers, artists, musicians, and actors keep working until they die.
[02:48.01]To these people, their work is their lives.